	<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="no" ?>
<modDesc descVersion="64">
    <author>Simdala, G.Albert, Mirackulix, Julian F. Modding, G.Albert, Simdala</author>
    <version>1.5.0.0</version>
    <title>
        <en>International 86 Series</en>
    </title>
    <description>
		
        <de>
            <![CDATA[International 86 Series (886, 986, 1086, 1486, 1586)

Preis: 54700 €

Die "International Harvester Company" (IH) entstand 1902 durch den Zusammenschluss der "McCormick Harvesting Machine Company" und der "Deering Harvester Company". 
Das Unternehmen hatte eine Reihe früher Traktormodelle. Der "Farmall" löste 1924 eine Revolution im Traktorendesign aus und führte den Dreirad-Reihentraktor ein. 
Er konnte nicht nur pflügen, sondern war auch zu Präzisionsarbeiten wie dem Kultivieren fähig - Damals eine echte Innovation. 
Die landwirtschaftliche Sparte von "International Harvester" wurde 1985 mit der "J. I. Case Company" fusioniert. Die Geräte werden immer noch unter dem Namen "Case IH" hergestellt.

Die Serie 86 von "International Harvester" wurde von 1976 - 1981 im IH-Werk Rock Island, Illinois, USA produziert, insgesamt liefen 47.420 Modelle dieser Serie dort vom Band.
Verkauft wurde der International 86 vor Allem auf dem nordamerikanischen Markt, in Europa war dieser Traktor nicht verfügbar, da es hier eigene, in Neuss (Deutschland) hergestellte Modelle des Herstellers gab (1056, 1255, 1455 etc.).
Neben John Deere war International Harvester in den 70er und 80er Jahren eine der meistverkauftesten Traktormarken, oftmals gab es zwischen eben diesen Marken einen kleinen eigenen Markenkrieg ("Team Green" oder "Team Red").
Technsich gesehen war an der Serie 86 innovativ, dass sie erstmals dafür designt wurde, eine vollwertige Kabine zu haben und den Fahrer in den Mittelpunkt des Schleppers rückte.
Dadurch wirkt der Traktor relativ kurz, hat aber eigentlich nahezu den gleichen Radstand wie vergleichbare Modelle anderer Hersteller, die in den Jahren seiner Produktion am Markt verfügbar waren.
Der Traktor hat ein 16-Gang Schaltgetriebe und eine hydraulisch unterstützte Lenkung. Die Motorleistung beträgt zwischen 95 und 179 PS und wird erzeugt von einem International Harvester 6-Zylinder-Dieselmotor mit 6,8l Hubraum.
Abgelöst wurde die Serie 86 im Jahr 1981 von der Serie 88, die einige Verbesserungen und ein neues Haubendesign mit sich brachte.

Änderungsprotokoll 1.1.0.5
-Erste Melodie der Auspuffwerte
- Getriebeübersetzungen geändert, von einem 4-Gang- auf ein 2-Gang-Getriebe geändert
-Türen entfernt
- Fügen Sie das Breitrad-Setup aus der RWD-Version als Option für die 4WD-Konfiguration hinzu.
--Erstellen Sie Motorkonfigurationen <280 PS ]]>
        </de>
		
        <en>
            <![CDATA[International 86 Series (886, 986, 1086, 1486, 1586)

Price: 54700 $

The "International Harvester Company" (IH) was created in 1902 through the merger of the "McCormick Harvesting Machine Company" and the "Deering Harvester Company".
The company had a number of early tractor models. The "Farmall" started a revolution in tractor design in 1924 and introduced the three-wheel in-line tractor.
Not only could it plow, but it was also capable of precision work such as cultivation - a real innovation at the time.
The agricultural division of "International Harvester" was merged with the "J. I. Case Company" in 1985. The machinery is still manufactured under the name "Case IH" today.

The Series 86 from "International Harvester" was produced from 1976 to 1981 at IH's Rock Island, Illinois, USA plant, with a total of 47,420 models of this series rolling off the production line.
The IH 86 was mainly sold on the North American market; this tractor was not available in Europe because the manufacturer had its own models made in Neuss (Germany) (1056, 1255, 1455 etc.) there.
Alongside John Deere, International Harvester was one of the best-selling tractor brands in the 70s and 80s, and there was often a small brand war between these brands in the US (team green or team red).
From a technical point of view, what was innovative about the Series 86 was that it was designed for the first time to have a fully-fledged cab and the focus was on the driver, putting him in the middle of the tractor.
This makes the tractor appear relatively short, but actually the 86 Series has almost the same wheelbase as comparable models from other manufacturers that were available on the market during the years of its production.
The tractor has a 16-speed manual transmission and power-assisted steering. The engine output is between 95 and 179 hp and is generated by an International Harvester 6-cylinder diesel engine with a displacement of 6.8 liters.
The series was replaced in 1981 by the series 88, which brought some improvements and a new bonnet design. 

Change log 1.1.0.5 
-First tune of Exhaust Values
-Gear ratios changed, Changed from a 4-speed to a 2-speed transmission
-Doors removed
-Add the Wide Wheel setup from the RWD version as an option for the 4WD configuration.
--Create engine configurations <280 HP]]>
        </en>
	
         <fr>
            <![CDATA[Série International 86 (886, 986, 1086, 1486, 1586)

Prix : 54700 €

La "International Harvester Company" (IH) a été créée en 1902 par la fusion de la "McCormick Harvesting Machine Company" et de la "Deering Harvester Company".
L'entreprise possédait un certain nombre de premiers modèles de tracteurs. Le "Farmall" a lancé une révolution dans la conception des tracteurs en 1924 et a introduit le tracteur en ligne à trois roues.
Non seulement il pouvait labourer, mais il était également capable de travaux de précision comme le travail du sol - une véritable innovation à l'époque.
La division agricole de "International Harvester" a fusionné avec la "J. I. Case Company" en 1985. La machinerie est toujours fabriquée aujourd'hui sous le nom de "Case IH".

La série 86 de "International Harvester" a été produite de 1976 à 1981 dans l'usine IH de Rock Island, Illinois, États-Unis, avec un total de 47 420 modèles de cette série sortant de la chaîne de production.
L'IH 86 a été principalement vendu sur le marché nord-américain ; ce tracteur n'était pas disponible en Europe car le constructeur y faisait fabriquer ses propres modèles à Neuss (Allemagne) (1056, 1255, 1455 etc.).
Aux côtés de John Deere, International Harvester était l'une des marques de tracteurs les plus vendues dans les années 70 et 80, et il y avait souvent une petite guerre de marque entre ces marques aux États-Unis (équipe verte ou équipe rouge).
D'un point de vue technique, l'innovation de la Série 86 était qu'elle était conçue pour la première fois pour avoir une cabine à part entière et que l'accent était mis sur le conducteur, le plaçant au milieu du tracteur.
Cela fait paraître le tracteur relativement court, mais en réalité, la série 86 a presque le même empattement que les modèles comparables d'autres fabricants qui étaient disponibles sur le marché pendant les années de sa production.
Le tracteur a une transmission manuelle à 16 vitesses et une direction assistée. La puissance du moteur est comprise entre 95 et 179 ch et est générée par un moteur diesel 6 cylindres International Harvester d'une cylindrée de 6,8 litres.
La série a été remplacée en 1981 par la série 88, qui a apporté quelques améliorations et un nouveau design de capot. ]]>
        </fr>
		
    </description>
    <iconFilename>modIcon.png</iconFilename>
    <multiplayer supported="true" />

    <storeItems>
        <storeItem xmlFilename="JFM_IH_86.xml"/>
    </storeItems>
	
	<brands>
        <brand name="FOURWHEELDRIVEE" title="4WD Michelin" image="$data/store/brands/brand_michelin.dds" />
        <brand name="TWOWHEELDRIVEE" title="2WD Michelin" image="$data/store/brands/brand_michelin.dds" />
		<brand name="TRELLEBORGFOURWHEELDRIVEE" title="4WD Trelleborg" image="$data/store/brands/brand_trelleborg.dds" />
    </brands>

	<l10n>
		<text name="configuration_ROWCROPSINGLE"><en>Single Rowcrops</en><de>"Rowcrop"-Reifen</de></text>
		<text name="configuration_TIRESINGLE"><en>Wide Tire</en><de>Breitreifen</de></text>
		<text name="configuration_ROWCROPDUAL"><en>Dual Rowcrops</en><de>"Rowcrop"-Doppelreifen</de></text>
		<text name="configuration_ONLYLEFTDUAL"><en>Ploughing Setup</en><de>Pflug-Setup</de></text>
		<text name="configuration_INTERIOR"><en>Interior Design</en><de>Kabinenausstattung</de></text>
		<text name="configuration_STANDARDBLACK"><en>Standard Black</en><de>Standard Schwarz</de></text>
		<text name="configuration_REDEDITION"><en>Red Edition</en><de>Red Edition</de></text>
		<text name="configuration_WESTERN"><en>"Western" (Premium)</en><de>"Western" (Premium)</de></text>
		<text name="configuration_FRONTLOADER"><en>Attachments</en><de>Anbauten</de></text>
		<text name="configuration_WEIGHT1"><en>Weight 1000kg</en><de>Gewicht 1000kg</de></text>
		<text name="configuration_WEIGHT2"><en>Weight 1500kg</en><de>Gewicht 1500kg</de></text>
		<text name="configuration_WEIGHT3"><en>Weight 2000kg</en><de>Gewicht 2000kg</de></text>
		<text name="configuration_WEIGHT4"><en>Weight 2500kg</en><de>Gewicht 2500kg</de></text>
		<text name="configuration_YESFRONTLOADER"><en>Quicke Console</en><de>Quicke Konsole</de></text>
		<text name="configuration_NOFRONTLOADER"><en>No</en><de>Nein</de></text>
		<text name="configuration_EXHAUSTPIPE"><en>Exhaust</en><de>Auspuff</de></text>
		<text name="configuration_STANDARDPIPE"><en>Standard</en><de>Standard</de></text>
		<text name="configuration_CURVEDPIPE"><en>Curved Pipe</en><de>Edelstahlrohr</de></text>
		<text name="configuration_SHORTPIPE"><en>Short Pipe</en><de>Kurzes Edelstahlrohr</de></text>
		<text name="configuration_ROWCROPSINGLEWIDEE"><en>Wide Rowcrops</en><de>Breite "Rowcrops"</de></text>
		<text name="configuration_TRANSM"><en>IH Torque Amplifier (Manual)</en><de>IH Torque Amplifier (Manuell)</de></text>
		<text name="configuration_WEIGHT"><en>Weights</en><de>Gewichte</de></text>
		<text name="configuration_NOWEIGHT"><en>No Weight</en><de>Keine Gewichte</de></text>
		<text name="configuration_MUDGUARD"><en>Mudguards</en><de>Keine Gewichte</de></text>
		<text name="configuration_COVERED"><en>Covered</en><de>Bedeckt</de></text>
		<text name="configuration_OPEN"><en>Open</en><de>Offen</de></text>
		
</l10n>

</modDesc>
